Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Publications
  - Bulletins on school architecture & hygiene for the U.S. Office of Education
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 13, 1917 2
King, Grace Jan. 20, 1917 2
McDonald, W.R. Jan. 24, 1917 2
West,A.F. Jan. 24, 1917 2
Smyth, Jefferson L. Jan. 25, 1917 2
McDonald, W.R. Jan. 29, 1917 2
Alleman, L.J. Feb. 2, 1917 2
Ittner, W.B. Feb. 2, 1917 2
Wilson, C.E. Feb. 3, 1917 2
McDonald, Mr. Feb. 10, 1917 2
Smith, Edith Feb. 10, 1917 2
Wardlaw, J.C. Feb. 12, 1917 2
McClure, Mr. Feb. 20, 1917 2
Sleight, George N. Feb. 20, 1917 2
Roy, V.L. Feb. 23, 1917 2
Bennett, H.E. Feb. 24, 1917 2
Lee, Joseph Feb. 24, 1917 2
Paul, August E. Feb. 24, 1917 2
Putnam, Helen C. Feb. 24, 1917 2
Schoenhals, M.K. March 12, 191 2
Wolcott, John D. March 12, 191 2
Claxton, P.P. March 16, 191 2
Lindberg, Lydia March 17, 191 2
Claxton, P.P. March 26, 191 2
Ellis, Mabel Brown March 26, 191 2
Hall, R.C. March 26, 191 2
Nichol, Julia H. April 19, 1917 2
Sisson, E.O. May 16, 1917 2
McClure, John R. May 25, 1917 2
Webster, Joseph May 31, 1917 2
Claxton, P.P. July 15, 1917 2
Goldsberry, Mrs. July 19, 1917 2
Claxton, P.P. Aug. 17, 1917 2
Porter, Mr. Aug. 28, 1917 2
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 25, 1917 2
Feagin, W.F. Sept. 28, 1917 2
Boykin, J.C. Oct. 27, 1917 2
Blount, Villma Nov. 5, 1917 2
Baish, H.H. Nov. 19, 1917 2
Hargraves, J.J. Nov. 19, 1917 2
Kistler, A.H. Nov. 30, 1917 2
Wood, Thomas D. March 29, 191 1
Barnwell, C.H. March 31, 191 1
Devendorf, B.A. March 31, 191 1
N.O. Nelson Manufacturing Co. March 31, 191 1
Speed, James March 31, 191 1
Thompson, Nath March 31, 191 1
Wolff & Company March 31, 191 1
Brewster, Wales C. April 2, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. April 2, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice G. April 2, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. April 2, 1913 1
Robinson, J.E. April 2, 1913 1
Speed, James April 2, 1913 1
Greeley, Allan April 3, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. April 3, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. April 4, 1913 1
Small, Willard S. April 4, 1913 1
Duncan, George W. April 5, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. April 5, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas Denison April 5, 1913 1
Perrett, T.E. April 8, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. April 8, 1913 1
Cheney, Charles H. April 9, 1913 1
Fegley, H. Winslow April 9, 1913 1
Hillyer, Thomas A. April 9, 1913 1
Kerns, Marshall April 9, 1913 1
Ludlow & Peabody April 9, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. April 10, 1913 1
Caldwell, James E. April 10, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. April 10, 1913 1
Doelle, Jonathan A. April 10, 1913 1
Roderick, J.F. April 10, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. April 11, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. April 12, 1913 1
Cheney, Charles H. April 12, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. April 12, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. April 12, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice G. April 12, 1913 1
Pullman Ventilator Mfg. Co. April 12, 1913 1
Monahan, A.C. April 14, 1913 1
Payne, Bruce R. April 14, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. April 14, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. April 16, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. April 16, 1913 1
Barber, Charles I. April 17, 1913 1
Keboch, F.D. April 17, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. April 17, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. April 17, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. April 18, 1913 1
Newman, Montrose K. April 18, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. April 19, 1913 1
Fegley, H. Winslow April 19, 1913 1
Corwin, R.W. April 21, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice G. April 21, 1913 1
Thomas, C.W. April 21, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas Denison April 21, 1913 1
Bruce, William George April 23, 1913 1
Cheney, Charles H. April 23, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. April 23, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice G. April 23, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. April 23, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. April 24, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. April 24, 1913 1
Brown, Henry E. April 24, 1913 1
Doelle, Jonathan A. April 24, 1913 1
Mark, E.H. April 24, 1913 1
Bruce, William C. April 25, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. April 25, 1913 1
Keboch, F.D. April 25, 1913 1
Ellis, Mabel Brown April 26, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. April 26, 1913 1
Bruce, William C. April 28, 1913 1
Ludlow & Peabody, Architects April 28, 1913 1
Mandel Brothers April 28, 1913 1
National Incinerator Co. April 28, 1913 1
Sanford, E.C. April 28, 1913 1
Mark, E.H. April 29, 1913 1
Brewster, Wales C. April 30, 1913 1
Bruce, William C. April 30, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. April 30, 1913 1
Pullman Automatic Ventilator April 30, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. April 30, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. May 1, 1913 1
Jassop, W.H. May 1, 1913 1
Johnson, Ruben May 1, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. May 1, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. May 1, 1913 1
Ittner, William B. May 5, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. May 5, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. May 5, 1913 1
Culver County Public Schools May 6, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. May 6, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. May 6, 1913 1
Brown, Henry E. May 8, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. May 10, 1913 1
Morris, Agnes May 10, 1913 1
Virtue & Co. May 13, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. May 13, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. May 14, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. May 19, 1913 1
James, George F. May 19, 1913 1
Doelle, Jonathan A. May 31, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. May 31, 1913 1
Richardson, Mr. & Mrs. J.B. May 31, 1913 1
Bierly, H.E. June 2, 1913 1
Brown, Henry E. June 2, 1913 1
Claxton, P.O. June 2, 1913 1
Gignilliat, L.R. June 2, 1913 1
James, George F. June 2, 1913 1
Mundy, H.H. June 2, 1913 1
Storey, Thomas A. June 2, 1913 1
Virtue & Co. June 2, 1913 1
Cheney, C.H. June 3, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. June 3, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. June 3, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. June 3, 1913 1
Gunn, Selskar M. June 3, 1913 1
Walker, W.B., Jr. June 3, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. June 3, 1913 1
Mundy, H.H. June 6, 1913 1
Conditt, Abbie June 7, 1913 1
Corwin, R.W. June 7, 1913 1
Ellis, Mabel Brown June 7, 1913 1
Fuii,W.G. June 7, 1913 1
Walker, W.B. June 7, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. June 7, 1913 1
Brewster, Wales C. June 9, 1913 1
Cheney, Charles H. June 9, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. June 9, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. June 9, 1913 1
Perkins, D.H. June 9, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. June 9, 1913 1
Springer, D.W. June 9, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. June 9, 1913 1
Houghton Mifflin Co. June 10, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. June 10, 1913 1
Conditt, Abbie June 12, 1913 1
Burnham, William C. June 13, 1913 1
Doelle, Jonathan A. June 13, 1913 1
Houghton Mifflin Co. June 13, 1913 1
Perkins, D.H. June 13, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. June 14, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. June 14, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. June 15, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. June 16, 1913 1
Callahan, E.L. June 16, 1913 1
Corwin, R.W. June 16, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. June 16, 1913 1
Hodgson, Casper W. June 16, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. June 16, 1913 1
Vogel, H.G. June 16, 1913 1
Dobbyn, F.W. June 17, 1913 1
Wray, George B. June 17, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. June 21, 1913 1
Callahan, E.B. June 21, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. June 21, 1913 1
Elliott, E.F. June 21, 1913 1
Mundy, H.H. June 21, 1913 1
Walker, W.B., Jr. June 21, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. June 23, 1913 1
Goldsberry, L.D. June 26, 1913 1
Miller, Donald H. June 26, 1913 1
Winship, A.E. June 26, 1913 1
Ludlow & Peabody, Architects June 28, 1913 1
Bogan, William J. Sept. 11, 1913 1
Broome, Joseph Sept. 11, 1913 1
Cheney, Charles Henry Sept. 11, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 11, 1913 1
Walcott, J.D. Sept. 11, 1913 1
Berry, M.W. Sept. 12, 1913 1
Brower, A.S. Sept. 12, 1913 1
Coggin, Mrs. S.R. Sept. 12, 1913 1
Cooke, John W. Sept. 12, 1913 1
Kalbach (sic), L.A. Sept. 12, 1913 1
Rapeer, Lewis Sept. 12, 1913 1
Rich, Josephine Arnold Sept. 12, 1913 1
Shute, Mrs. H.J. Sept. 12, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 13, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Sept. 13, 1913 1
Che Plakas, Constantin Sept. 15, 1913 1
Humphrey, Mrs. Charles G. Sept. 15, 1913 1
Tharp, S.M. Sept. 15, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 18, 1913 1
Cook, John W. Sept. 18, 1913 1
Fitzpatrick, F.B. Sept. 18, 1913 1
Holland, E.O. Sept. 18, 1913 1
Perkins, Fellows & Hamilton Sept. 18, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 20, 1913 1
Platt, J. Mills Sept. 20, 1913 1
Baruch, Bertha Hirsch Sept. 22, 1913 1
Bateman, Mrs. C.C. Sept. 22, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 22, 1913 1
Hyatt, Edward Sept. 22, 1913 1
Naramore, F.A. Sept. 22, 1913 1
Ellis, Carlos B. Sept. 23, 1913 1
Ellis, Carlos B. Sept. 23, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 24, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 24, 1913 1
O’Neil, J.H. Sept. 24, 1913 1
Mairs, Thomas I. Sept. 24, 1913 1
Alltucker, Margaret M. Sept. 25, 1913 1
Chapin, Clara C. Sept. 26, 1913 1
Cherry, H.H. Sept. 26, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Sept. 26, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 27, 1913 1
Engelhard, V.H. Sept. 27, 1913 1
Ferrell, John A. Sept. 27, 1913 1
Hanson-Bellows Co. Oct. 8, 1913 1
Kingsley, Sherman Oct. 8, 1913 1
Parks, M.M. Dec. 5, 1917 2
Peterson, E.A. Dec. 12, 1917 2
Kelly, RoyW. Dec. 15, 1917 2
Finney, Ross L. Dec. 21, 1917 2
Baker, N.R. Jan. 7, 1918 3
Wood, Alice H. Jan. 15, 1918 3
Wood, Thomas D. Jan. 15, 1918 3
Boykin, J.C. Jan. 16, 1918 3
Chapman, J. Virgil Jan. 16, 1918 3
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 16, 1918 3
Haltom, L.H. Jan. 21, 1918 2
Crichlow, J.H. Jan. 23, 1918 2
Regen & Weller, Architects Feb. 1, 1918 3
Woodden, Eli Feb. 9, 1918 3
Woodden, Eli Feb. 9, 1918 3
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 14, 1918 3
Luckie, W.V. Feb. 14, 1918 3
Ramsey, J.W. Feb. 19, 1918 3
Boykin, NFN March 7, 1918 3
Elizabeth McCormick Memorial March 7, 1918 2
Small, Willard S. March 23, 191 3
Bush, L.L. March 28, 191 3
Denney, C.C. April 4, 1918 3
Carter, E.E. April 17, 1918 3
Rogers, Margaret Y. April 17, 1918 3
Wright, Owen B. April 17, 1918 3
Treen, Karl April 26, 1918 3
Vermilion, H.F. April 26, 1918 3
Claxton, P.P. May 14, 1918 3
Bower, Grover C. May 18, 1918 3
Cooper, Frank Irving May 22, 1918 3
Claxton, P.P. June 7, 1918 2
Claxton, P.P. July 20, 1918 3
Stewart, NFN July 27, 1918 3
Waller, George D. Aug. 9, 1918 3
Claxton, P.P. Aug. 26, 1918 3
Gilbert, H.C. Aug. 29, 1918 3
Spratling, Mrs. M.A. Aug. 29, 1918 3
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 14, 1918 3
Dean, L.A. Sept. 14, 1918 3
Johnson, Helen Lansing Sept. 14, 1918 3
Dean, L.A. Sept. 20, 1918 3
Dean, L.A. Sept. 26, 1918 3
Dean, L.A. Oct. 16, 1918 3
Windes, E.E. Oct. 16, 1918 3
Dean, L.A. Nov. 8, 1918 3
Chenault, Robert N. Dec. 13, 1918 3
Dukes, A.J. Dec. 13, 1918 3
Foster, James Dec. 13, 1918 3
Foster, James Dec. 13, 1918 3
Pontius, Isaac Jan. 16, 1919 3
Decker, A. I. Jan. 10, 1919 3
Buckley, H.M. Jan. 25, 1919 3
Dowell, Spright Jan. 27, 1919 3
Buice, W.A. Jan. 29, 1918 3
Small, W.S. Feb. 1, 1919 3
Tucker, E.B. Feb. 1, 1919 3
Manley, J.B. Feb. 3, 1919 3
Minkel, L.H. Feb. 6, 1919 3
Blackwell, Walter R.L. Feb. 13, 1919 3
Johnson, W.P. Feb. 15, 1919 3
Buckley, H.M. Feb. 19, 1919 2
North, E.M. Feb. 24, 1919 3
Reynolds, R.J. Feb. 24, 1919 3
Threlfall, LV. March 4, 1919 3
Parsons, Mary S. March 7, 1919 3
Patterson, E.W. March 7, 1919 3
Baker, N.R. March 18, 191 3
Daniel, R.P. March 18, 191 3
Perrin, Ambrose March 18, 191 3
Bedford, Lois March 24, 191 3
Bawden, William T. April?, 1919 3
Tucker, E.B. April?, 1919 3
Friffee, Arthur H. April 10, 1919 3
John Latenser & Sons April 10, 1919 3
Small, W.S. April 10, 1919 3
Wilder, Theo April 10, 1919 3
Morrison, W.P. April 16, 1919 3
Bennett, Twitty & Reese May 8, 1919 3
Buice, W.A. May 8, 1919 3
Duffey, H.S. May 8, 1919 3
Wolcott, Theresa H. May 8, 1919 3
Lavery, D. May 19, 1919 3
Thomas, David E. May 20, 1919 3
Bennett, Twitty & Reese May 21, 1919 3
Claxton, P.P. June 7, 1919 3
Mead, Clarence G. June 7, 1919 3
Blakeley, H.B. June 16, 1919 3
Chamblis, R. Lee June 16, 1919 3
Clark, Walter E. June 16, 1919 3
Bennett, Twitty & Reese June 18, 1919 3
Griggs, W.C. Sept. 27, 1919 3
Bryan, T.J. Sept. 29, 1919 3
Rupert, W.W. Sept. 29, 1919 3
Cherry, H.H. Oct. 1, 1919 3
Able, J.F. Oct. 16, 1919 3
Miller, Lola Oct. 16, 1919 3
Woodring, A.P. Oct. 16, 1919 3
Griggs, W.C. Oct. 18, 1919 3
Rupert, W.W. Oct. 18, 1919 3
Lucey, Michael H. Oct. 26, 1919 3
Stoltzfus, J.H. Oct. 26, 1919 3
Easley, Owen R. Oct. 30, 1919 3
Morrison, W.J. Oct. 30, 1919 3
Rhodes, L.T. Oct. 30, 1919 3
Rosenkoeter, C.H. Oct. 30, 1919 3
Stone, May Oct. 30, 1919 3
Chenault, Robert N. Oct. 31, 1919 3
Cowart, R.W. Nov. 1, 1919 3
Gove, W.E. Nov. 1, 1919 3
Cheanult, Robert N. Nov. 4, 1919 3
Clayton, Aline Nov. 4, 1919 3
Goldsberry, Louise D. Nov. 4, 1919 3
Brunimer, Rose L. Nov. 17, 1919 3
Harrington, A.C. Nov. 17, 1919 3
Henry, Esther E. Nov. 17, 1919 3
Hovey, George Rice Nov. 17, 1919 3
Cameron, Norman W. Nov. 19, 191 3
Cummings, Grace Nov. 19, 1919 3
Imhof, Orris M. Nov. 19, 1919 3
Seizer, F.l. Nov. 20, 1919 3
Mills, Hubert H. Nov. 21, 1919 3
Suhrie, Ambrose L. Nov. 21, 1919 3
Todd, John W. Nov. 21, 1919 3
Yelland, W.R. Nov. 21, 1919 3
McLellan, J.B. Nov. 22, 1919 3
McQuilkin, D.E. Nov. 22, 1919 3
Griggs, W.C. Nov. 24, 1919 3
Shackelford, E.M. Dec. 1, 1919 3
Sharp, L.A. Dec. 1, 1919 3
Chenault, Robert N. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Corbin, A.F. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Cowart, R.W. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Elliott, A.E. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Griggs, Mr. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Jenkins, L.W. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Jones, R.R. Dec. 13, 191 3
McClellan, J.B. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Netcott & Netcott Dec. 13, 1919 3
Redfern, J.E. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Stegal, B.M. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Tighe, Richard J. Dec. 13, 1919 3
Atkinson, Otto Dec. 15, 1919 3
Baker, N.R. Dec. 23, 1919 3
Carpenter, Harry A. Dec. 23, 1919 3
Earl, E.O. Dec. 23, 1919 3
Eichelberger, James W. Dec. 23, 1919 3
Pelton, A.C. Dec. 23, 1919 3
Robinson, William McKinley Dec. 23, 1919 3
Sharp, L.A. Dec. 23, 1919 3
Holt, Elizabeth C. Jan. 5, 1920 3
Howell, Harry Feb. 26, 1920 3
Chapman, Virgil March 4, 1920 3
Holt, Elizabeth March 11, 192 3
Pratt, Linwood March 19, 192 3
Moore, W.E. April 29, 1920 3
Holt, Elizabeth C. June 3, 1920 3
Twiss, George I. June 16, 1920 3
Phelps, C.E. June 22, 1920 3
Nash, Mary E. June 30, 1920 3
Temple, H.R. June 30, 1920 3
Claxton, P.P. July 1, 1920 3
Claxton, P.P. July 27, 1920 3
Bawden, W.T. Aug. 3, 1920 3
Beckham, Mary C. Aug. 3, 1920 3
Bawden, W.T. Aug. 14, 1920 3
Lowrey, Harvey H. Sept. 20, 1920 3
Calhoun, J.T. Nov. 1, 1920 3
Holt, Elizabeth C. Nov. 27, 1920 3
Keller, W.K. Nov. 27, 1920 3
Miller, W.E. Dec. 12, 1920 3
Avent, Joseph E. Jan. 8, 1921 3
Unidentified Jan. 15, 1921 3
Page, Frank R. Jan. 20, 1921 3
Stephens, Edwin L. Jan. 20, 1921 3
Cater, Anna L. Feb. 7, 1921 3
Hildebrandt, H.A. Feb. 7, 1921 3
Schnittkind, Henry T. Feb. 26, 1921 3
Schnittkind, Henry T. Feb. 26, 1921 3
Hall, Maurice C. March 7, 1921 3
Ragle, Horace N. March 7, 1921 3
Able, J.F. March 11, 192 3
Claxton, P.P. March 11, 192 3
Claxton, P.P. March 17, 192 3
Kalbach, L.A. March 17, 192 3
Baker, B.B. March 24, 192 3
Lang, A.B. March 24, 192 3
Cady, Bertha Chapman March 28, 192 3
Cornwell, Irene M. March 28, 192 3
King, Jeannette March 31, 192 3
Holt, Elizabeth C. April 6, 1921 3
Ricker, Maurice April 9, 1921 3
Baker, B.B. April 23, 1921 3
Bawden, William T. April 23, 1921 3
Turner, Jessie April 23, 1921 3
Abercrombie, John W. April 25, 1921 3
Benns, W.E. April 26, 1921 3
Foote, Irving T. April 27, 1921 3
Long, Raymond V. April 27, 1921 3
Baker, B.B. April 30, 1921 3
Bawden, William T. May 7, 1921 3
Foote, Irving May 30, 1921 3
Tigert, John J. July 1, 1921 3
Bischoff, Carl H. July 2, 1921 3
Roberts, Ezra C. July 2, 1921 3
Goldsberry, Louise D. Aug. 22, 1921 3
Small, W.S. Aug. 22, 1921 3
Small, W.S. Aug. 22, 1921 3
Schnittkind, Henry T. Aug. 23, 1921 3
Baker, Milo Aug. 24, 1921 3
Blair, John J. Sept. 3, 1921 3
Small, W.S. Sept. 3, 1921 3
Small, Willard S. Sept. 6, 1921 3
Blair, John J. Sept. 8, 1921 3
Kalbach, L.A. Sept. 12, 1921 3
Benson, W.W. Sept. 17, 1921 3
Boykin, J.C. Sept. 21, 1921 3
Goldsberry, Louise D. Sept. 22, 1921 3
Goldsberry, Louise D. Sept. 22, 1921 3
Small, Willard S. Sept. 22, 1921 3
Freeman, J.E. Sept. 26, 1921 3
Small, W.S. Sept. 26, 1921 3
Stephens, Dr. Setp. 26, 1921 3
Kalbach, L.A. Oct. 5, 1921 3
Smaii,Willard S. Oct. 10, 1921 3
Small, W.S. Oct. 26, 1921 3
Small, W.S. Oct. n.d., 1921 3
Small, Willard S. Nov. 13, 1921 3
Sibley, James L. Nov. 19, 1921 3
Pennington, Pleasant Nov. 29, 1921 3
Spooner, H.L. Dec. 17, 1921 3
Welborn, Allen Dec. 17, 1921 3
Blair, John J. Dec. 27, 1921 3
Conner, W.A. Jan. 19, 1922 3
Kalbach, L.A. Jan. 19, 1922 3
Wood, Alice C. Jan. 19, 1922 3
Dickey, Clarence W. Feb. 4, 1922 3
Tigett, John J. Feb. 4, 1922 3
Wood, Thomas D. Feb. 9, 1922 3
Small, W.S. Feb. 25, 1922 3
Small, W.S. March 23, 192 3
District Secretary April 1, 1922 3
Kalbach, L.A. April 1, 1922 3
Tappan, Julia B. April 1, 1922 3
Walker, Robin A. April 1, 1922 3
Kalbach, L.A. April 24, 1922 3
Tappan, Julie April 24, 1922 3
Madison, Frederick D. May 17, 1922 3
Kalbach, L.A. May 17, 1922 3
Kalbach, L.A. May 27, 1922 3
Warnica, S.V. June 1, 1922 3
Manufacturers’ Record June 15, 1922 3
Snow, O.E. June 26, 1922 3
Wolman, Abel June 26, 1922 3
Robinson, E.O. June 29, 1922 3
Tigert, John J. July 1, 1922 3
Harman, A. F. July 13, 1922 3
Millison, J. July 20, 1922 3
Tidball, Lewis C. July 20, 1922 3
Surgeon General July 22, 1922 3
Lucas Jean, Sallie Aug. 5, 1922 3
Blair, John J. Sept. 11, 1922 3
Hatcher, Lee Sept. 11, 1922 3
Wilby, Frank Oct. 5, 1922 3
Gould, Florence H. Oct. 7, 1922 3
Roberts, J. Platt Oct. 7, 1922 3
Small, Willard S. Oct. 7, 1922 3
Risley, James H. Oct. 11, 1922 3
Buttrick, Wallace Oct. 12, 1922 3
Cook, A.E. Oct. 18, 1922 3
Miller, Kate B. Oct. 18, 1922 3
Small, W.S. Oct. 18, 1922 3
Martin, J.O. Oct. 19, 1922 3
Miller, Kate B. Oct. 30, 1922 3
Bogart, Peter B. Nov. 1, 1922 3
Hill, Henry H. Nov. 1, 1922 3
American Warming & Ventilatin Nov. 23, 1922 3
Klabach, L.A. Nov. 23, 1922 3
Small, W.S. Nov. 23, 1922 3
Carr, J.W. Dec. 6, 1922 3
Wedgwood, Harriet Dec. 6, 1922 3
Wedgwood, Harriet Dec. 13, 1922 3
Neild, Edward F. Dec. 14, 1922 3
Stillwell, Erie G. Dec. 14, 1922 3
Wedgwood, Harriet Jan. 5, 1923 3
Cooper, Frank Irving Jan. 13, 1923 3
Van Buskirk, E.F. Jan. 23, 1923 3
Welborn, O.M. Feb. 5, 1923 3
Lockhart, K.E. Feb. 15, 1923 3
Betelle, James 0. March 1, 1923 3
Abel, J.F. April 2, 1923 3
Bawden, William T. April 2, 1923 3
Cook, Katherine M. April 10, 1923 3
Nunn, Roscoe April 21, 1923 3
Crittenden, B.K. April 28, 1923 3
Long, Raymond V. April 28, 1923 3
Kupfer, H.W. May 26, 1923 3
Bawden, William T. June 14, 1923 3
Hirst, C.M. June 14, 1923 3
Bawden, William T. June 20, 1923 3
Commissioner June 25, 1923 3
Kalbach, L.A. July 2, 1923 3
Oppen, Lucy July 2, 1923 3
Kalbach, L.A. July 7, 1923 3
Credle, W.F. July 9, 1923 3
Allen, James E. July 25, 1923 3
Ittner, W.B. Aug. 4, 1923 3
Blair, J.J. Aug. 22, 1923 3
Bawden, W.F. Aug. 30, 1923 3
Blair, Jonathan J. Sept. 29, 1923 3
Boykin, J.C. Sept. 29, 1923 3
Boykin, J.C. Oct. 4, 1923 3
Cooper, Frank Irving Oct. 4, 1923 3
Boykin, J.C. Oct. 5, 1923 3
Kranz, J.R. Oct. 26, 1923 3
Wedgwood, Harriet Nov. 1, 1923 3
Calhoun, J.T. Nov. 1, 1923 3
Boykin, J.C. Nov. 8, 1923 3
Horton, Rouchen Nov. 8, 1923 3
Moore, D.H. Nov. 26, 1923 3
Ivy, H.M. Dec. 4, 1923 3
Burris, Mr. Dec. 10, 1923 3
Roemer, Joseph Dec. 13, 1923 3
Rogers, J.F. Dec. 13, 1923 3
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 13, 1923 3
Wright, C.K. Dec. 13, 1923 3
Bethune, Mary M. Jan. 19, 1924 3
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 19, 1924 3
Corbett, D.D. Jan. 19, 1924 3
Macmillan Company Jan. 19, 1924 3
Ivy, H.M. March 4, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. March 5, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. March 5, 1924 3
Russell, Frederick F. March 15, 192 3
Bethune, Mary McCloud March 20, 192 3
Hinman, Jack J., Jr. April 14, 1924 3
McAndrews, William April 17, 1924 3
Wimbs,Ad April 28, 1924 3
Cook, Katherine M. May 8, 1924 3
Exner, M.J. June 12, 1924 3
Jolloway, J.W., Jr. June 12, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. June 14, 1924 3
Schucker, L.R. June 26, 1924 3
McMullen, E.W. June 28, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. July 2, 1924 3
Benson, W.W. July 17, 1924 3
Burdette, H.S. July 17, 1924 3
Kalbach, L.A. July 17, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. July 17, 1924 3
Boykin, James C. Aug. 6, 1922 3
Rogers, J.F. Sept. 10, 1924 3
Nolan, William T. Oct. 2, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. Nov. 1, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. Nov. 6, 1924 3
Thomas, D.E. 1924-11-01 3
Ramsey, E.E. Dec. 29, 1924 3
Tigert, John J. Dec. 29, 1924 3
Rogers, J.F. Jan. 2, 19125 3
Rogers, J.F. Jan. 3, 1925 3
Poundstone, O.C. Jan. 17, 1925 3
Bethune, Mary McLoud Jan. 22, 1925 3
Furgeson, Marion Feb. 25, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. March 7, 1925 3
Kalbach, L.A. March 9, 1925 3
Papy, Loca E. March 30, 192 3
Rogers, J.F. April 3, 1925 3
Bigelow,M.A. April 11, 1925 3
Johnson, Sexton April 21, 1925 3
Peebles & Ferguson, Architects April 23, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. May 6, 1925 3
Hodge, Maud May 7, 1925 3
Kelly, Lessie V. May 14, 1925 3
Roemer, Joseph May 15, 1925 3
Wood,Thomas D. May 15, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. June 5, 1925 3
Bryan, William Lowe June 11, 1925 3
Weary, E.D. June 12, 1925 3
Roberts, Jack June 30, 1925 3
Northrup, W.C. July 2, 1925 3
Powe & Williamson July 2, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. July 2, 1925 3
Zook, George F. July 2, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. July 17, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. Aug. 3, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. Sept. 2, 1925 3
Palmore, R.A. Sept. 14, 1925 3
Palmore, R.A. Sept. 15, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. Oct. 3, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. Oct. 7, 1925 3
Bakke, Ella Cyrene Oct. 22, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. Nov. 2, 1925 3
Reynolds, Nora L. Nov. 23, 1925 3
Wilbur, G. Elmer Nov. 23, 1925 3
Curtis, W.R. Nov. 30, 1925 3
Storey, Thomas A. Nov. 30, 1925 3
Rogers, J.F. Dec. 2, 1925 3
Exner, M.J. Dec. 12, 1925 3
Pleasant, J.L. Dec. 23, 1925 3
Nash, M.A. Jan. 5, 1926 3
Broom, J.W. Jan. 8, 1926 3
Laramy, R.E. Jan. 26, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Jan. 27, 1926 3
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 11, 1926 3
Clark, Harry Feb. 27, 1926 3
Storey, Thomas A. Feb. 27, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. March 2, 1926 3
Kalbach, L.A. March 4, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. March 4, 1926 3
Miller, Bessie A. March 8, 1926 3
Payne, President March 8, 1926 3
Adams, Robert April 7, 1926 3
Adams, Robert April 7, 1926 3
Kalbach, L.A. April 19, 1926 3
Laramy, Robert April 21, 1926 3
Eicher, Hubert C. May 5, 1926 3
Young, R.O. July 27, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. July 29, 1926 3
Thomas, Adelbert A. Aug. 26, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Aug. 28, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Aug. 28, 1926 3
Blanton, R.S. Sept. 3, 1926 3
Reid, Frank K. Sept. 3, 1926 3
Pruett, Haskell Sept. 16, 1926 3
Rowe, L.S. Sept. 16, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Sept. 30, 1926 3
Haaga, Theressa Oct. 7, 1926 3
Holt, Elizabeth C. Oct. 21, 1926 3
Menon, K.B. Oct. 21, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Oct. 30, 1926 3
Bruce, William C. Nov. 9, 1926 3
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 14, 1926 3
Pruett, Haskell Nov. 14, 1926 3
Jackson, Mrs. H.E. Nov. 23, 1926 3
Bryan, William lowe Nov. 29, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Nov. 29, 1926 3
Rogers, J.F. Dec. 30, 1926 3
Moser, Mr. Jan. 3, 1927 3
Braden, W.H. Jan. 7, 1927 3
Earley, Albert Jan. 7, 1927 3
Menon, K.B. Jan. 7, 1927 3
Barber & McMurry, Architects Jan. 13, 1927 3
Chumber, Roy 0. Jan. 13, 1927 3
Donovan, John J. Jan. 13, 1927 3
Jenkins, F.C. Jan. 13, 1927 3
Sibley, James E. Jan. 13, 1927 3
Tucker, President Jan. 13, 1927 3
Ranck, F.E. Jan. 14, 1927 3
Jenkins, Frank C. Jan. 16, 1927 3
Brown, Allye Mae Jan. 21, 1927 3
Kalbach. L.A. Jan. 21, 1927 3
Tucker, E.B. Jan. 21, 1927 3
McAfee, L.F. Jan. 22, 1927 3
Mennen, K.D. Jan. 22, 1927 3
Sibley, James E. Jan. 22, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. Jan. 22, 1927 3
Stone, May Jan. 22, 1927 3
McCuistion, Fred Jan. 26, 1927 3
Ireland, Allen G. Jan. 27, 1927 3
Mitchell, Morris Jan. 27, 1927 3
Braden, W.H. Jan. 28, 1927 3
Jrouse, P.G. Jan. 28, 1927 3
Jrouse, P.G. Jan. 29, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. Jan. 29, 1927 3
Buchner, Edward Feb. 7, 1927 3
Shofstall, W.P. Feb. 19, 1927 3
Butler, George D. Feb. 23, 1927 3
Esper, George J. Feb. 23, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. Feb. 28, 1927 3
Chumber, Roy 0. March 1, 1927 3
Smith, J.F. March 1, 1927 3
Tucker, E.B. March 14, 192 3
Palmore, R.A. March 21, 192 3
Barber, Charles I. March 30, 192 3
Hunkins, L.E. March 30, 192 3
Swetman, Ralph W. March 30, 192 3
Tucker, E.B. March 30, 192 3
Burns, L.W. April 1, 1927 3
Cralle, Robert E. April 1, 1927 3
Hall, Mary April 1, 1927 3
Mulvihill, Philip April 1, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. April 1, 1927 3
Stone, May April 1, 1927 3
Lowery, Lawrence T. April 6, 1927 3
Mozee, 8. 8. April 11, 1927 3
Sandmeier, M.A. April 11, 1927 3
Challman, Samuel A. April 15, 1927 3
Cralle, Robert E. April 15, 1927 3
Mulvihill, Philip April 15, 1927 3
Fenn, Donald F. April 20, 1927 3
McCuistion, Fred April 20, 1927 3
Swetman, Ralph W. April 25, 1927 3
Sydenham, Laura M. April 25, 1927 3
Esper, George J. April 29, 1927 3
Rogers, J.F. April 30, 1927 3
Harmon, A.F. May 2, 1927 3
Lowery, Lawrence T. May 3, 1927 3
Berry, Mrs. May 13, 1927 3
Tucker, E.B. May 13, 1927 3
Adams, Robert H. May 20, 1927 3
Henry, J.H. May 20, 1927 3
Lowery, Lawrence T. May 20, 1928 3
Hirst, C.M. May 25, 1927 3
Lowrey, Lawrence T. May 25, 1927 3